适配器初始化完毕后我们就把它绑定到Listview
Once the adapter is initialized, let's bind it to the ListView.
但你会发现我们的fragment里
But you may notice that we don't have a reference to the ListView
还缺少这个ListView的引用
in our fragment.
它只是在XML布局中定义了
It was only defined in the layout XML.
系统找到XML布局文件
The system takes and inflates layout XML files,
转换成一个完整的树状图
and turns them into a full view hierarchy
而且主activity的树状图顶端有一个根布局
with a root layout of the main activity at the very top of the view tree.
我们可以给每个视图赋予ID
We can also assign IDs to each view in the tree,
如果不需要的话也可以不赋予ID
but it's not required if you don't need a reference to an individual view.
就像这个ImageView没有指明ID也没关系
For example, this ImageView doesn't have an ID associated with it and that's okay.
在与之相关的Activity或者fragment的Java代码里
Within the Java code of the associated activity or fragment,
如果需要引用一个按钮  只要调用findViewById方法就好了
if we need a reference to the button, we can simply call findViewById,
这个方法会沿着树状图查找
which will traverse down the view hierarchy until it finds a view
找到对应ID的按钮才返回
with an ID button, and then it will return that.
类似地  我们也能在树状图中找到
Similarly, we can traverse down the view hierarchy to find the linear layout
ID叫container的线性布局  然后返回
with the ID container, and then return that.
对于这个TextView的引用本来
We could do the same to find a reference to this TextView
也可以通过遍历树状图来查找
by traversing down the view hierarchy.
但注意到我们已经有了这个TextView
But you'll notice that we already have a reference to the container
父布局的ID也就是container
which is the direct parent of this TextView.
因此  我们调用container.findViewById
Hence, we can just call container.findViewById
就可以在这个子树里找到这个TextView的ID
to search this subtree to find the TextView with this ID,
然后返回
and then return it.
用这个技巧  我们就通过子树查到要找的视图
With this method, we have a smaller sub-tree to search for a given view,
而不是去全树遍历
as opposed to searching the entire view hierarchy.
在Android官方Java文档的View类中
In the Android Java doc for the View class,
就是下面这个链接
which is linked below if you want to follow along,
有一个已经在XML布局中定义的按钮的例子
it contains an example with a button with Define in Layout XML.
它的ID是my_button
It was assigned an ID, my_button.
然后在这个Activity里我们可以使用findViewByID方法
Then, in the Activity, we can use the findViewByID method with that ID,
来引用这个按钮
so that we can get a reference to the button.
然后还可以动态修改
Then we can change it dynamically,
比如给它加一个点击监听器
such as by adding a click listener to it.
那现在 PLaceholderFragment 类里将适配器绑定到ListView里
Now in the Placeholder Fragment class, bind the adapter to the ListView.
由于我们给 ListView 之前指定了ID
Luckily, we did assign an ID to the ListView earlier,
现在可以很容易找到了
so we can find it easily now.
记得找到树状图里的最小子树
Think about the smallest sub-tree in the view hierarchy
再去调用 findViewByID 方法  最后设置 ArrayAdapter
that you can call findViewByID on, then set the adapter on it.
如果还需要范例的话  请你查看下面的链接
If you want an example, you can see one in the link below.
完成后记得勾上这些框框
Check the boxes when you're done.